{
    "subject": "resource/Hod_Stuart",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Canada",
    "human_readable": "Hod Stuart was born in Canada.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9129385352134705,
            "question": "Is Hod Stuart Canadian?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8922208547592163,
            "question": "Where was Hod Stuart born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8894654512405396,
            "question": "Does Hod Stuart have any siblings or relatives who were also born in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8178754448890686,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Canada who share Hod Stuart's birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5682490468025208,
            "question": "What is the name of Hod Stuart's hometown in Canada?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5430955290794373,
            "question": "What country is Hod Stuart from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5355249047279358,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Hod Stuart's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4181707799434662,
            "question": "What is Hod Stuart known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3310759365558624,
            "question": "Where might Hod Stuart currently reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20777331292629242,
            "question": "Does Hod Stuart have any notable accomplishments?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hod Stuart was born in Canada.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6581_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might Hod Stuart currently reside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6581_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Hod Stuart known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6581_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Hod Stuart's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6581_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6581_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents state that Hod Stuart was born on February 20, 1879, in Ottawa, Ontario, Canada (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6581/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6581/re-ranker-msmarco/83.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that Hod Stuart was born on February 20, 1879, in Ottawa, Ontario, which is part of Canada. Therefore, the statement \"Hod Stuart was born in Canada\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}